You guys are all so careful.
I have to say,
you two are quite a match.
No wonder Xu Qingdao
wanted to set you two up.
Shut up.
[Eclipse in the Lost City] [Episode 19]
What...
What's happening to me?
Don't kill me.
I don't know anything.
I don't know.
I don't have the antidote.
Antidote?
What antidote?
Wolf...
Wolfbane antidote.
Tell me.
Who's behind you?
Xu Qingdao.
He's behind all of this.
I just keep the maintenance doses for him.
He has all the antidotes.
I don't know anything else.
Then why did the Shisha Gang members die
after being injected
with the maintenance dose?
The maintenance dose can
ease the effects of the poison,
but there are risks.
Everyone reacts differently.
He was given S-02.
His body couldn't handle it, so he died.
What do the numbers mean?
Talk.
The higher the number,
the stronger the drug's effects,
the more the body can tolerate,
and the more addictive it becomes.
But once you survive it,
the Wolfbane binds more effectively
with the body.
Why did Xu Qingdao make you do this?
Who is behind him?
I...
I don't know.
I really don't know.
I have a heart condition.
Medicine...
Where is it?
Save me.
I'll tell you everything.
Give it to me.
Tell me.
What does the antidote look like?
The...
The antidote is...
Blue...
He definitely knows more than this.
Looks like we'll have to take our time
interrogating him.
How about we take him back
to the Qingtian Gang?
What did you take?
Spit it out.
This isn't heart medicine.
He planned to kill himself all along.
Xu Yin.
You killed him?
He killed himself.
Hurry up.
See if we can find any other clues.
Strange.
Why have the private accounts been
losing so much money these past few months?
[Ningcheng Railway Station—
Western Medicine Cargo List]
[Ningcheng Railway Station—Imported
Western Military Medicine Cargo List]
So the hospital switched
to a new equipment supplier,
cutting the director out
of his usual supply deals,
and costing him a lot in kickbacks.
They are all working for the foreigners.
Back then, to curry favor
with the foreigners
and become the vice president
of the chamber of commerce,
Xu Qingdao tampered with the arrangements.
He replaced the original suppliers
with them.
They already had a grudge.
Then we've got an easy way in.
You want to frame Xu Qingdao?
Interesting.
True.
Since things have already come this far,
we might as well
muddy the waters a bit more.
But...
what evidence are we going to use?
You forgot?
Xu Qingdao wants my kidney.
Before the surgery,
blood needs to be drawn for matching.
The sample will be kept for a while.
[Xu Qingdao]
All done.
[Ningcheng Police Station]
Director,
the director of Renji Hospital is dead.
What?
Don't let this leak out,
especially to the press.
Think about it.
I just came back from a meeting
in the provincial capital,
and now we've got a dead body
on our hands.
This is gonna kill me.
Not a word.
If you do, this quarter's bonus is gone.
We need to keep this under wraps.
Got it?
Yes.
But do you want to take a look
at the results of our evidence collection?
Right, right, right.
Who did it?
We found Xu Qingdao's cufflink
on the director.
And this report
shows that the blood found on the director
matches Xu Qingdao's blood type.
So I suspect it was murder.
Stop, stop, stop.
Neither of them is easy to mess with.
Here's what we'll do.
Just say there's not enough evidence.
Yes.
[Blood Comparison Test Report]
Sir,
everything has been arranged.
We've also kept the hospital incident
under wraps.
Xu Qingdao
still doesn't know you've found out.
Not a word will leak out.
Xu Qingdao has been asking around
about who blocked his way
into the chamber of commerce.
He did suspect the director.
After all, for that extra 30% in profits,
he promised to replace the equipment
in every hospital in Ningcheng
with foreign-made goods.
That meant
the director wouldn't get
a single penny in kickbacks.
I didn't expect him to be so bold.
Call him
and tell him to come see me.
Yes.
According to the director,
Xu Qingdao has been running
an experiment involving the Wolfbane.
What exactly does he want to do?
Maybe he doesn't know, either.
Makes sense.
The Shisha Gang is just a sharp knife.
If we want the answer,
we must catch the person
holding the knife as soon as possible.
I'll be discharged tomorrow.
You still have a fever.
You need to get some rest.
I can't wait any longer.
The longer we leave this unsolved,
the more dangerous Ningcheng becomes.
Alright.
Got it, Officer Shen.
A little bribe for the savior.
Tianbai.
I'm relieved to see you're okay.
Thank you, Chief.
Don't mention it.
No need to be so formal with me.
We'll be family soon.
Tea gets weaker
after being brewed too many times.
Sitting in the same position
for over a decade
gets boring.
You are right, Chief.
Water flows downhill,
but people climb upward.
Sometimes,
you just have to bow your head.
The Shisha Gang may look powerful,
but for all these years,
I've always had someone
more powerful breathing down my neck.
I call him... Sir.
Sir?
He
helped me a lot once.
But I don't owe him anything anymore.
After drinking leftover tea
for so many years,
it's time for a fresh pot.
Tianbai,
do you understand what I mean?
Rest assured, Chief.
I'll give everything I have
to the Shisha Gang and to you.
Good.
Father.
Yin?
Miss Xu,
let me do it.
Father,
I have a favor to ask of you.
What is it?
Your birthday is coming up.
I ordered you a suit
from a newly opened tailor shop
in the concession.
If you have time this afternoon,
you can go try it on.
If it doesn't fit, they can alter it.
This afternoon...
Chief.
The owner of that tailor shop
is Howard's brother.
He only moved to Ningcheng recently.
Howard?
The director
of the Industrial and Commercial Bureau.
Yin,
that's very thoughtful of you.
I'll go with you.
Tianbai,
you come along, too.
Okay.
I've cut the phone line.
[12 hours ago]
No one can get through.
They can only send messages by letter,
and I've intercepted those, too.
Unfortunately, I still can't
find the messenger.
[2 p.m. tomorrow, Dashijie]
As expected,
we guessed right.
The director and Xu Qingdao
are both working for Sir.
The director is dead,
and Xu Qingdao's blood
was found at the scene.
No matter what,
Sir whould confront him
and demand answers.
Xu Qingdao hasn't noticed, right?
The police have kept it under wraps.
That old man still doesn't know
he's being made the scapegoat.
I was planning to keep the director alive
and see what we could get out of him.
But now that he's dead,
we'll just have to play along.
You want to drive a wedge
between Xu Qingdao and Sir?
Exactly.
We need to make each of them
believe the other is about to make a move.
Once there's a crack
in their relationship,
they'll leave an opening.
We absolutely cannot
let them meet tomorrow.
I'll leave the Shisha Gang to you.
I'll go to Dashijie and lie in wait.